sillybandz.com 2011-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Buy SillyBrandz

**CONDITIONS OF USE**  
Welcome to sillybrandzglobal.com, a division of BCP Imports, LLC.

BCP Imports, LLC. provides their services to you subject to the following conditions. Please take the time to read them carefully.

We understand that your trust is our most important asset. We are committed to the protection and proper use of your personal information. We are further committed to maintaining an understanding of the products and services you find to be most valuable. We respect your privacy and take great care to safeguard information in our possession.

**WE DO NOT AND WILL NOT SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD-PARTIES.** ** **

**ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS**  
When you visit a Silly brandz website or send an e-mail to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

**COPYRIGHT**  
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of BCP Imports, LLC. or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of BCP Imports, LLC. and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.

**TRADEMARKS**  
BCP Imports, LLC. and other marks indicated on our site are registered trademarks of BCP Imports, LLC. All other trademarks not owned by BCP Imports, LLC. or its subsidiaries that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by BCP Imports, LLC. or its subsidiaries.

**LICENSE AND SITE ACCESS**  
BCP Imports, LLC. grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, with-out express written consent of BCP Imports, LLC. The license granted does not include resale or commercial use of this site or its contents; any collection and use of product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this site or its contents; downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, spiders, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of BCP Imports, LLC. You may not use any meta tags or any other "hidden text" utilizing the BCP Imports, LLC. name or trademarks without the express written consent of BCP Imports, LLC. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of BCP Imports, LLC. and our affiliates without express written consent. Any unauthorized use terminates the permission or license granted by BCP Imports, LLC.

**COPYRIGHT COMPLAINTS**  
BCP Imports, LLC. respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please feel free to contact us via telephone, mail or electronic mail.

**RISK OF LOSS OR DAMAGE**  
All items purchased from BCP Imports, LLC. are made in accordance to a shipment contract. The risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier. A claim must be made with the carrier prior to the product being replaced. 

**PRODUCT DESCRIPTIONS**  
BCP Imports, LLC. and it’s staff attempt to be as accurate as possible on description of products. In order to assure that the customer receives the color of choice we use the PMS color chart or “Pantone Matching System” as computer monitor settings will effect the look or shade of a color. We recommend that the customer find a physical copy of the PMS color chart and match their color accordingly. Be advised that BCP Imports, LLC. will not and can not be held responsible for colors chosen incorrectly.

**SITE POLICIES, MODIFICATION, AND SEVERABILITY**  
Please take the time to review our other policies, such as our privacy policy, posted on this site.. We reserve the right to make changes to our site, policies, and these conditions of use at any time. If any of these conditions shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining condition.

**WE DO NOT AND WILL NOT SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD-PARTIES.**  
\- We do not Collect information through cookies.  
\- We do not sell or share any collected information with anyone.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
You must be 13 years of age or older to communicate with BCP Imports, LLC. We collect various types of information depending on how you use our site. When you order from us, we collect your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, and phone number. Credit Card information is processed by VeriSign/Paypal Payment Services and is not kept on file at BCP Imports, LLC. 

**WE MAY USE YOUR CONTACT INFORMATION FOR NOTIFICATION AND TO SEEK CONSENT:**  
To improve the content on our Web site. For example, we may use log files to find out which parts of our site or our products are visited most often.

For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we send out email notifications to our customers about products or events that we think may be of interest to them. Marketing and promotional emails will be sent to everyone who enters an email on the website and musrt be at least 13 years of age. You will be asked to opt-in. Recipients will be provided with a return email address or another Internet-based response mechanism that allows a recipient to opt out of future email messages to that email address.

BCP Imports, LLC Maintains the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information collected.

BCP Imports, LLC does not collect information from tchildrenunder the age of 13 and fully complies to The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.
